Half Zombie. Half Demon. All Zemon!
Dead Before Dawn is a adventure, comedy, horror film directed by April Mullen.
A bunch of college kids accidentally unleash an evil curse that causes people
to kill themselves and turn into Zombie Demons, aka ZEMONS!
Casper Galloway, played by Devon Bostick.
Charlotte Baker, played by Martha MacIsaac.
Horus Galloway, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Dazzle Darlington, played by Brandon Jay McLaren.
Lucy Winthrop, played by Brittany Allen.
Patrick Bishop, played by Kyle Schmid.
Dead Before Dawn (also known as Dead Before Dawn 3D) is a 2012 Canadian adventure-horror comedy directed by April
Mullen, written by Tim Doiron, and starring Devon Bostick, Martha MacIsaac, and Christopher Lloyd.
It introduces "zemons", a combination of zombie and demon.
It is Canada's first stereoscopic live-action 3D feature film, and Mullen is the
first woman to direct a live-action, fully stereoscopic 3D feature film.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.